Guide to the Harris Masterson I papers,1860-1942, bulk 1880-1920 MS 468
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Legal Correspondence / Court Documents, 1893-1917 (Boxes 132-189)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Houston Town Lot Improvement Co. v. Wansbrough, 1906 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Greene v. Masterson (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Goree v. Bayou City Realty Co., 1912 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: TX Bank Trust Co. of Galveston v. Miller (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Smith v. Sherman, 1911-1912 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Houston v. Masterson, 1917 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Broocks (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Hardin Lumber Co. v. Allen (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Schwarz v. Pye (Box 150, Folder 16)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Fordtran (Box 150, Folder 17)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Bright Turner, 1899 (Box 150, Folder 18)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Brooks Lanier, 1903 (Box 150, Folder 19)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: TX Bank Trust Co. v. Miller the Vaundun Co., 1910 (Box 150, Folder 20)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Suits involving L.N. Yarborough (Box 150, Folder 21)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Kapham v. Indemnity Co. of America (Box 150, Folder 22)
  - 55th Judicial District of TX, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Pickle (Box 150, Folder 23)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Kinney v. Oxford Telephone Mfg. Co. (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Ragley (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Culpepper, 1912 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: J.B. Sweeney v. E.H. Sweeney, 1913 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Harlingen Land Water Co., 1915 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Greene (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cage v. Kent, 1917 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Commonwealth Trust Co. of Houston v. Bailey, 1914 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Broocks, 1911 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Appel, 1909 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Downey, 1908 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Alexander, 1911 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cockburn v. Albrecht, 1915 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Medford (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Lewis, 1905 (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Hill, 1914 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Central Bank Trust v. Pye, 1911 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Yarborough v. Clarkson (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Union National Bank v. Pye, 1911 (Box 151, Folder 19)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: S.H. Kress Co. of TX v. Allen (Box 151, Folder 20)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cunningham v. Fordtran (Box 151, Folder 21)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Houston Town Lot Improvement Co. v. Green, 1913 (Box 151, Folder 22)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Carnes, 1912 (Box 151, Folder 23)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Clark (Box 151, Folder 24)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Duesenberry v. Jewett (Box 151, Folder 25)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Frantz Frantz v. Masterson (Box 151, Folder 26)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: TX Town Lot Improvement Co. v. Boyd, 1912 (Box 151, Folder 27)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Chambers (Box 151, Folder 28)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Turner v. Keyworth (Box 151, Folder 29)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Croom v. Blakely, 1918 (Box 151, Folder 30)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Fordtran v. Luhn, 1907 (Box 151, Folder 31)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Powell Bros. Sanders Co., Ltd., 1906 (Box 151, Folder 32)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Freed v. Pye, 1911 (Box 151, Folder 33)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Forbes v. Forbes, 1910 (Box 151, Folder 34)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Johnson v. Masterson, 1910 (Box 151, Folder 35)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: James v. Jackson, 1908 (Box 151, Folder 36)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Chase v. Houston Town Lot Improvement Co., 1915 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Harlingen Land Co., 1915 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Rice Institute v. League, 1918 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Beazley, 1914 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Harris, 1908 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cunningham v. Wright, 1914 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Anderson, 1914 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Kemp v. Babcock, 1904 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cline v. Malevinsky (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Jordan v. Jordan, 1906 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Ross, 1914 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Foster v. Gulf, CO Santa Fe Ry. Co. (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Perry v. Masterson, 1913 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Ragley, 1913 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Dunman v. Hermann, 1904 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Davidson, 1909 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Calloway v. Mayes (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Central Trust Co. v. Smith (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Jenkins v. Lester, 1909 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Albert v. unknown Lang heirs, 1913 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. R.S. Sterling Investment Co., 1918 (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Rowan, 1906 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Commercial Fire Insurance Co. v. Corbett (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Elmore v. Saulnier, 1916 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Central Bank Trust Co. of Houston v. Hill (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Davis v. Davis, 1914 (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Tod, 1916 (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Woodburn v. TX Town Lot Improvement Co., 1911 (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: TX Town Lot Improvement Co. v. Michigan Fire Marine Insurance Co., 1911 (Box 152, Folder 29)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. De La Vergne Machine Co, 1917 (Box 152, Folder 30)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Central Bank Trust Co. v. Jones (Box 152, Folder 31)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Nelson v. Turner, 1919 (Box 152, Folder 32)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Morgan v. Hardin Lumber Co, 1914 (Box 152, Folder 33)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Bering v. Green (Box 152, Folder 34)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Kemp v. Babcock (Box 152, Folder 35)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cunningham v. Fordtran, 1910 (Box 152, Folder 36)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Frantz v. Masterson, 1910 (Box 152, Folder 37)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Rowan, 1910 (Box 152, Folder 38)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Island City Woodworking Co. v. Pye (Box 152, Folder 39)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Atwood v. Hudson, 1914 (Box 152, Folder 40)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: 61st District Court summons (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Hailey, 1921 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Sutherland v. Austin, 1923 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Ragley v. Houston Oil Co. (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Blakely v. Vaughan (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Duffie, 1913 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cage v. Wier Broocks (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Wynn (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Tod, 1916 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Santa Helena Improvement Co., 1918 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Dupree v. Brown (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Broocks, 1921 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Anderson v. Bishop, 1921 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Phelps v. Smith (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Magnolia Provision Co. v. Allen (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Kempner v. Allen, 1911 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: TX Town Lot Improvement Co. v. Welschmeyer, 1909 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Roberts v. Converse, 1912 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Dillehunt v. Masterson, 1918 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cullen v. Allen, 1907 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Wells v. Masterson, 1916 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Wright, 1912 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cravens v. Oliver, 1920 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cravens Cage Co. v. Bergin, 1921 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Cravens Cage Co. v. Nini, 1921 (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Masterson v. House, 1912 (Box 153, Folder 26)
  - 61st Judicial District, Harris Co.: Joachim v. Sour Lake Development Co. (Box 153, Folder 27)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Bayou City Realty Co. (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson Irrigation Co. v. King (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Harvin (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Lee Land Co., 1919 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: State of Texas v. Block, 1923 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Hill (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson Smith v. Humphreys Oil Co., 1923 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Austin Rusk Realty Co. v. Masterson Cage, 1923 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Robers, 1912 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Louis v. S. Samuels Co., 1919 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Freeman v. SD TX Oil Co., 1916 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: State of Texas v. Cage, 1918 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Burgner v. Burgner, 1917 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Emmert v. Masterson (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Hudging v. Schaff, 1918 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Fitch v. Bayou City Realty Co., 1914 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Hite (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Jordan v. Rogers, 1918 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Johnson v. Johnson, 1920 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Murphy v. Murphy (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Rogers v. Masterson, 1919 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Lyons (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Shepard, 1916 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Clark, 1916 (Box 154, Folder 24)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Taylor, 1922 (Box 154, Folder 25)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Bartell v. Holman, 1924 (Box 154, Folder 26)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. unknown Childress heirs (Box 154, Folder 27)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Bingham v. Masterson, 1921 (Box 154, Folder 28)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Stewart v. Cage, 1922 (Box 154, Folder 29)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Tuttle (Box 154, Folder 30)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Odom (Box 154, Folder 31)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Putnam, 1919 (Box 154, Folder 32)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Cage v. Stimson, 1921 (Box 154, Folder 33)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. E.L. Witt Sons (Box 154, Folder 34)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Davis (Box 154, Folder 35)
  - 80th District Court, Harris Co.: Masterson v. Jones (Box 154, Folder 36)
  - Anderson District Court: Cronin v. St. Paul Fire Marine Ins. Co. (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Bastrop District Court: Elgin Light Power Co. v. Rice, 1911 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Bastrop District Court: Calcasieu Lumber Co. v. Rice, 1917 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Bexar District Court: H.P. Drought Co. v. Stewart, 1923 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Bexar District Court: TX Motor Car Co. v. Guthrie, 1911 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Bexar District Court: Masterson v. Closner, 1915 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - 57th District Court: Nix v. Withers, 1915 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - 57th District Court: Masterson v. Hillje, 1915 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - 73rd District Court: Masterson v. Federal Bank Trust Co., 1916 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Bexar District Court: Banks v. Dupree (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Bosque District Court: 1st National Bank of Morgan v. Kittrell (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Burleson District Court: Carter v. Masterson (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Callahan District Court: Jackson v. Masterson, 1903 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - Cameron District Court: Masterson v. Canott (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - Cameron District Court: Villareal v. Villareal, 1920 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - Cameron District Court: Lorber v. Hill (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - Cameron District Court: MN-TX Land Irrigation Co. v. LaFeria Mutual Canal Co. (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Cameron District Court: Masterson v. Cameron Co. Irrigation District #1 (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Cameron District Court: Masterson v. Watson, 1916 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - Cameron District Court: Rio Grande Canal Co. v. Masterson, 1919 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - Cameron District Court: Rio Grande Canal Co. v. Hill (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - Cameron District Court: Reed v. Wilkerson (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - Cameron District Court: Villareal v. Briggs (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - Cameron District Court: Palmetal Co. v. Harlingen Land Water Co., 1919 (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - Cameron District Court: Skelton v. Masterson (Box 155, Folder 25)
  - Cameron District Court: Fremont Investment Co. v. Philpott, 1919 (Box 155, Folder 26)
  - Cameron District Court: Lowe v. Palmetal Co., 1915 (Box 155, Folder 27)
  - Cameron District Court: Rio Grande Canal Co. v. Masterson (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - Cameron District Court: Carey v. Masterson, 1921 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - Cameron District Court: Mid-Continent Life Insurance Co. v. Hill, 1916 (Box 155, Folder 30)
  - Cameron District Court: Leysaht v. Bishop, 1922 (Box 155, Folder 31)
  - Cameron District Court: 28th various (Box 155, Folder 32)
  - Cameron District Court: Buel v. Carey, 1922 (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - Cameron District Court: Rabb v. Lee, 1923 (Box 155, Folder 34)
  - Cameron District Court: State of Texas v. Masterson Cage, 1923 (Box 155, Folder 35)
  - Brazoria District Court: James A. Cato v. Robert J. Townes (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Brazoria District Court: J. G. Brown v. C. Davis (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Brazoria District Court: Sarah Brewster v. Brazoria Land Cattle Co. (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Brazoria District Court: L. W. Groce v. Alex Compton (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Brazoria District Court: Leonard Groce v. R. J. Townes (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Brazoria District Court: Hadden, Taylor, Co. v. J. E. Wilson (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Brazoria District Court: Margaret Bradhey v. T. G. Masterson 1874 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. J. E. Naylor 1895 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Brazoria District Court: Levi Jordan Estate (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Brazoria District Court: Elizabeth G. Wheelwright v. A. A. Holland 1901 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Brazoria District Court: A. R. Townes v. Albert Dade 1891 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. H. Wellman v. W. S. Hart 1900 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Brazoria District Court: F. W. Stevens v. William Disney 1892 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Brazoria District Court: Henry Austin v. H. Masterson 1896 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. B. Adams v. T. L. Smith 1892 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. A. J. Hawthorn 1901 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. J. R. Carney (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Brazoria District Court: E. N. Williams v. Chase. Brown (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Brazoria District Court: Estate of A. B. Brown 1872 (Box 156, Folder 19)
  - Brazoria District Court: Mahala Davis v. Barney Winston 1895 (Box 156, Folder 20)
  - Brazoria District Court: Gordon Brown v. T. L. Smith (Box 156, Folder 21)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. Robert Bennie 1897 (Box 156, Folder 22)
  - Brazoria District Court: C. Lund v. M. Chambers (Box 156, Folder 23)
  - Brazoria District Court: John Barnes v. C. C. Frankland (Box 156, Folder 24)
  - Brazoria District Court: W. F. Moore v. H. D. Adams 1886 (Box 156, Folder 25)
  - Brazoria District Court: Pompey Higgins v. H. Masterson 1897 (Box 156, Folder 26)
  - Brazoria District Court: Adove Lobit v. Lander Cleveland 1896 (Box 156, Folder 27)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. D. N. Phillips 1897 (Box 156, Folder 28)
  - Brazoria District Court: State of Texas v. A. C. Jenn 1896 (Box 156, Folder 29)
  - Brazoria District Court: C. Davis v. William Harvey 1892 (Box 156, Folder 30)
  - Brazoria District Court: Mary T. Minard v. Chase. Brown (Box 156, Folder 31)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. Cyrus Luse (Box 156, Folder 32)
  - Brazoria District Court: Terry Van Pelt v. T. L. Smith, Jr. (Box 156, Folder 33)
  - Brazoria District Court: Sam B. Dickinson Estate (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. B. Hansborough (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. W. Martin (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Brazoria District Court: Heirs of W. C. White J. Knight v. F. W. Stevens (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Brazoria District Court: R. W. Spencer v. C. C. Millican (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Brazoria District Court: C. E. Groce v. NY TX Land Co. Ltd. (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Brazoria District Court: A. W. Bascom v. C. Davis (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Brazoria District Court: J. H. Shapard v. J. T. Owen (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. C. C. Huntington (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Brazoria District Court: J. W. Slimp A. D. Stelzer v. C. O. Brown (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Brazoria District Court: Irene Moller v. South Texas Development Co. (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. Pompey Higgins (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. H. S. Smith (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. H. R. Stevens (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Brazoria District Court: L. M. Disney v. E. L. Stroud (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - Brazoria District Court: R. H. Barrow v. H. Masterson (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. L. M. Disney (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Brazoria District Court: L. M. Disney Deeds (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Brazoria District Court: Lee Farrer v. E. J. Hodges (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Brazoria District Court: Angleton State Bank v. E. J. Hodges (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Brazoria District Court: E. J. Hodges v. Angleton State Bank (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - Brazoria District Court: Elliot Cage v. W. S. Davis (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Brazoria District Court: Horace E. Kelly v. H. Masterson (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Brazoria District Court: J. S. Angier v. Branch T. Masterson (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Brazoria District Court: J. S. Angier v. Branch T. Masterson (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. C. R. Davis (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. J. H. Weems (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Brazoria District Court: Angleton State Bank v. P. M. Travis (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Brazoria District Court: A. S. Newson v. H. Masterson (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Brazoria District Court: Asa Mitchell Estate (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Brazoria District Court: C. R. Cox v. T. G. Masterson (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Brazoria District Court: William Kennedy Estate (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Brazoria District Court: Green B. Jamison Estate (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Brazoria District Court: T. Noel v. B. H. Wisdom (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Brazoria District Court: Minnie Wells v. H. Masterson (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Brazoria District Court: T. L. Smith v. C. Davis (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Brazoria District Court: H. Masterson v. L. M. Disney (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Chambers District Court: Masterson v. Harris, 1904 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Cherokee District Court: Sullivan v. Ducey, 1906 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Cherokee District Court: Smither v. Hutchings, Sealy Co., 1907 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Clay District Court: Snapp v. Merchants Planters Bank (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Clay District Court: Snapp v. Bishop, 1920-1921 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Coleman District Court: McCord v. Webb, 1906 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Colorado District Court: Kirby v. Countee, 1918 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Concho District Court: Jones v. unknown Heinrich heirs, 1907 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Concho District Court: Boyce v. Masterson, 1902 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Concho District Court: Boyce v. Bryson, 1904 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Dallas District Court: Hoeldtke v. Bishop, 1920 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. Cline, 1922 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. West, 1921 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. Sieger, 1921 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Dallas District Court: Guaranty State Bank Trust Co. v. Underwood (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Dallas District Court: Langdeau v. Daugherty, 1901 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. Jezek (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. Barrett (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. Martin, 1921 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. Elliot, 1920-1921 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Dallas District Court: Masterson v. Cline, 1921 (Box 159, Folder 21)